ozmodchips.com 2016-06-08

# Privacy Notice : OzModChips.com, Australian Supplier of x360k3y/xk3y, R4DS, Gateway3DS, Sky3DS+ and Cronus Max Plus

This site is owned and operated by Ozmodchips.com. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At Ozmodchips.com, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it. 

Definition of the Information Ozmodchips.com gathers and keeps track of. Ozmodchips.com gathers two types of information about users: 

  * Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive our electronic newsletters, to email a friend, and from participation in polls and surveys.
  * Information Ozmodchips.com gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers by better understand the demographics of our audience. Under no circumstances does Ozmodchips.com divulge any information about an individual user to a third party.

**CHILDREN**  
We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.

**USAGE TRACKING**  
Ozmodchips.com tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. Ozmodchips.com does break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser).  
Ozmodchips.com sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

**COOKIES**  
We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Ozmodchips.com uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above).You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use most of this website. 

**USE OF INFORMATION**  
Ozmodchips.com uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience on our website.  
As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters to subscribers once in a while. Newsletters might have important information about your console, or might be informing you of a new product. Ozmodchips.com NEVER shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners.  

**Order Fulfillment**  
If by any chance we are unable to send your order due to stock shortages or other reasons, we may need to share your information (just the address and item ordered) to an overseas company. If the companies we sometimes use do not have the item in stock then we have to sell your address to someone that does. If we do this, the warranty will be with the 3rd party company. This is extremely rare, and usually only happened with wholesale orders .  

**OPT-OUT POLICY**  
We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:  
\- Opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters.   
\- Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users 

**YOUR CONSENT**  
By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Ozmodchips.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
